(Sheldon:)I no longer stage spontaneous
biohazard drills after 10 p.m.
(Sheldon:)And I abandoned my goal
to master Tuvan throat singing.
-I shouldn't ask, but what is--?
-No.
[VOCALIZING]
(Sheldon(after demonstrating):)I'd be much further along
if I'd been allowed to practice.
(Leonard:)Look, Sheldon,
I know it's in the agreement.
(Leonard:)If you turn into a zombie,
I promise I will not kill you.
(Leonard:)In fact, I'll even let you eat my brains.
But I'm taking Penny to Switzerland.
(Sheldon:)-Is that your final decision?
-It is.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Penny:)It's not over, is it?
(Leonard:)What do you think?
[SHELDON VOCALIZING]
(Leonard:)Got a bit of traffic this morning, huh?